Guide to the Richard Maass Collection of Westchester and New York State 1645-1995, (Bulk: 1645-1910) MSS.055
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Printed Materials
  - Subseries A: Newspapers and Other Printed Materials
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2826 place: London, Jan 19, 1775; 055-005-A-0850; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2827 place: London, Jan 21, 1775; 055-005-A-0859; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2820 place: London, Jan 5, 1775; 055-005-A-0868; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2837 place: London, Feb 14, 1775; 055-005-A-0877; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2839 place: London, Feb 18, 1775; 055-005-A-0886; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no.2840 place: London, Feb 21, 1775; 055-005-A-0895; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The London Chronicle vol 37, no. 2841 place: London, Feb 23, 1775; 055-005-A-0904; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2834 place: London, Feb 7, 1775; 055-005-A-0913; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2864 place: London, Apr 18, 1775; 055-005-A-0922; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2867 place: London, Apr 25, 1775; 055-005-A-0931; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2869 place: London, Apr 29, 1775; 055-005-A-0940; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2879 place: London, May 23, 1775; 055-005-A-0949; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2896 place: London, Jul 1, 1775; 055-005-A-0958; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2900 place: London, Jul 11, 1775; 055-005-A-0967; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2907 place: London, Jul 27, 1775; 055-005-A-0976; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2898 place: London, Jul 6, 1775; 055-005-A-0985; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2887 place: London, Jun 10, 1775; 055-005-A-0994; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2890 place: London, Jun 17, 1775; 055-005-A-1003; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 37, no. 2885 place: London, Jun 6, 1775; 055-005-A-1012; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2909 place: London, Aug 1, 1775; 055-005-A-1021; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2914 place: London, Aug 12, 1775; 055-005-A-1030; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2917 place: London, Aug 19, 1775; 055-005-A-1039; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2910 place: London, Aug 3, 1775; 055-005-A-1048; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2929 (2 copies) place: London, Sep 16, 1775; 055-005-A-1057; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2930 place: London, Sep 19, 1775; 055-005-A-1066; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2931 place: London, Sep 21, 1775; 055-005-A-1075; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2935 place: London, Sep 30, 1775; 055-005-A-1084; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2926 place: London, Sep 9, 1775; 055-005-A-1093; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2953 place: London, Nov 11, 1775; 055-005-A-1102; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2958 place: London, Nov 23, 1775; 055-005-A-1111; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2950 place: London, Nov 4, 1775; 055-005-A-1120; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2944 place: London, Oct 21, 1775; 055-005-A-1129; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2967 place: London, Dec 14, 1775; 055-005-A-1138; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2968 place: London, Dec 16, 1775; 055-005-A-1147; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 38, no. 2970 place: London, Dec 21, 1775; 055-005-A-1156; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 39, no. 3046 place: London, Jun 15, 1776; 055-005-A-1165; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 39, no. 3043 place: London, Jun 8, 1776; 055-005-A-1174; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 39, no. 3027 place: London, May 2, 1776; 055-005-A-1183; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 39, no. 3035 place: London, May 21, 1776; 055-005-A-1192; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 39, no. 3037 place: London, May 25, 1776; 055-005-A-1201; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 41, no. 3132 place: London, Jan 2, 1777; 055-005-A-1210; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 42, no. 3260 place: London, Nov 11, 1777; 055-005-A-1219; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 42, no. 3257 place: London, Oct 21, 1777; 055-005-A-1228; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 48, no. 3749 place: London, Dec 12, 1780; 055-005-A-1237; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 47, no. 3621 place: London, Feb 19, 1780; 055-005-A-1246; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 47, no. 3652 place: London, May 2, 1780; 055-005-A-1255; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - The London Chronicle vol. 48, no. 3727 place: London, Oct 21, 1780; 055-005-A-1264; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The London Gazette no. 12181 place: London, Apr 24, 1781; 055-005-A-1273; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 19)
      physical description: full sheet in folio; newspaper
    - The London Gazette Extraordinary place: London, Dec 30, 1776; 055-005-A-1278; 8 pages (Box 14, Folder 19)
      physical description: 2 half sheets in folio, quired; newspaper
    - The London Gazette no. 11641 place: London, Feb 20, 1776; 055-005-A-1287; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - The London Gazette Extraordinary place: London, Oct 10, 1776; 055-005-A-1292; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 19)
      physical description: half sheet in folio; newspaper
    - Niles' Weekly Register vol. 38, no. 837, Lee's letter to Miss Franks, Dec. 20 1779 place: Baltimore, Sep 29, 1827; 055-005-A-1297; 16 pages (Box 14, Folder 20)
      physical description: single octavo gathering; magazine
      dimensions: 16cm x 25cm
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post vol. 2, no. 249 place: Philadelphia, Aug 24, 1776; 055-005-A-1314; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
      dimensions: 22cm x 27cm
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post vol. 1, no. 141 place: Philadelphia, Dec 16, 1775; 055-005-A-1319; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post vol. 3, no. 383 place: Philadelphia, Jul 26, 1777; 055-005-A-1324; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post vol. 2, no. 219 place: Philadelphia, Jun 15, 1776; 055-005-A-1329; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post vol. 2, no. 216 place: Philadelphia, Jun 8, 1776; 055-005-A-1334; 4 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
    - The Pennsylvania Evening Post no. 82, supplement place: Philadelphia, undated; 055-005-A-1339; 2 pages (Box 14, Folder 20.5)
      physical description: fragment; newspaper
      dimensions: 22cm x 25cm
    - The Boston Gazette, and Country Journal no. 1092 place: Watertown, Apr 22, 1776; 055-005-A-1392; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 21)
      dimensions: 26cm x 40cm
    - The Boston Gazette, and Country Journal no. 1178 place: Watertown, Apr 7, 1777; 055-005-A-1397; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - The Boston Gazette, and Country Journal no. 1124 place: Watertown, Dec 2, 1776; 055-005-A-1402; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - The Boston Gazette, and Country Journal no. 1114 place: Watertown, Sep 23, 1776; 055-005-A-1407; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 21)
      dimensions: 25cm x 39cm
    - The Caledonian Mercury no. 8490 place: Edinburgh, Apr 1, 1776; 055-005-A-1412; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
      dimensions: 28cm x 43cm
    - The Caledonian Mercury no. 8554 place: Edinburgh, Aug 5, 1776; 055-005-A-1417; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Caledonian Mercury no. 8476 place: Edinburgh, Feb 28, 1776; 055-005-A-1422; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Caledonian Mercury no. 8465 place: Edinburgh, Feb 3, 1776; 055-005-A-1427; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Caledonian Mercury no. 8512 place: Edinburgh, May 22, 1776; 055-005-A-1432; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Columbian Centinel & Massachusetts Federalist vol. 39, no. 2000 place: Boston, Jun 22, 1803; 055-005-A-1437; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 23)
      physical description: single folio; newspaper
      dimensions: 33cm x 50cm
    - The Connecticut Courant and Weekly Intelligencer no. 632 place: Hartford, Mar 3, 1777; 055-005-A-1442; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 24)
      dimensions: 27cm x 44cm
    - The Connecticut Courant and Weekly Intelligencer no. 922 place: Hartford, Sep 24, 1782; 055-005-A-1447; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 24)
      dimensions: 24cm x 35cm
    - The Connecticut Gazetter and the Universal Intelligencer vol. 14, no. 685 place: New London, Dec 27, 1776; 055-005-A-1452; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Connecticut Gazetter and the Universal Intelligencer vol. 14, no. 680 place: New London, Nov 22, 1776; 055-005-A-1457; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Connecticut Gazetter and the Universal Intelligencer vol. 14, no. 678 place: New London, Nov 8, 1776; 055-005-A-1462; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Connecticut Journal no. 494 place: New-Haven, Apr 2, 1777; 055-005-A-1467; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - The Connecticut Journal no. 629, mentions Benedict Arnold place: New-Haven, Nov 17, 1779; 055-005-A-1472; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Connecticut Observer vol. 5, no. 22 place: Hartford, May 25, 1829; 055-005-A-1477; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 27)
      dimensions: 37cm x 53cm
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 116 place: Boston, Aug 13, 1778; 055-005-A-1482; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 304 place: Boston, Dec 20, 1781; 055-005-A-1487; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 114 place: Boston, Jul 30, 1778; 055-005-A-1492; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 25 place: Boston, Nov 14, 1776; 055-005-A-1497; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 26 place: Boston, Nov 21, 1776; 055-005-A-1502; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
      dimensions 25cm x 39cm
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 27 place: Boston, Nov 28, 1776; 055-005-A-1507; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 23 place: Boston, Oct 31, 1776; 055-005-A-1512; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 124 place: Boston, Oct 8, 1778; 055-005-A-1517; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 16 place: Boston, Sep 12, 1776; 055-005-A-1522; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 18 place: Boston, Sep 26, 1776; 055-005-A-1527; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - The Continental Journal, and Weekly Advertiser no. 15 place: Boston, Sep 5, 1776; 055-005-A-1532; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Drewry's Berby Mercury vol. 49, no. 2527 place: Derby, Oct 6, 1780; 055-005-A-1537; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 29)
      dimensions: 32cm x 47cm
    - Dunlap's Pennsylvania Packet, or the General Advertiser vol. 6, no. 282 place: Philadelphia, Apr 8, 1777; 055-005-A-1542; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 30)
      dimensions: 26cm x 42cm
    - Dunlap's Pennsylvania Packet, or the General Advertiser vol. 6, no. 278 place: Philadelphia, Mar 11, 1777; 055-005-A-1547; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Dunlap's Pennsylvania Packet, or the General Advertiser no number place: Philadelphia, Oct 14, 1780; 055-005-A-1552; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - The Essex Gazette vol. 3, no. 142 place: Salem, Apr 16, 1771; 055-005-A-1557; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Essex Gazette vol. 4, no. 159 place: Salem, Aug 13, 1771; 055-005-A-1562; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The New England Chronicle: or, the Essex Gazette vol. 8, no. 390 place: Cambridge, Jan 18, 1776; 055-005-A-1567; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Essex Gazette vol. 3, no. 155 place: Salem, Jul 16, 1771; 055-005-A-1572; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Essex Gazette vol. 3, no. 149 place: Salem, Jun 4, 1771; 055-005-A-1577; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Essex Gazette vol. 4, no. 165 place: Salem, Sep 24, 1771; 055-005-A-1582; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - The Essex Journal and New-Hampshire Packet vol. 3, no. 126 place: Newbury-Port, Oct 18, 1776; 055-005-A-1587; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 32)
      dimensions: 25cm x 41cm
    - Essex Register vol. 25, no. 34 place: Salem, Apr 28, 1825; 055-005-A-1592; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 33)
      dimensions: 37cm x 52cm
    - The Evening Post; and the General Advertiser vol. 1, no. 11 place: Boston, Dec 26, 1778; 055-005-A-1597; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Exeter Watchman vol. 2, no. 31 place: Exeter, Apr 28, 1818; 055-005-A-1602; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 35)
      dimensions: 30cm x 52cm
    - The Farmer's Weekly Museum: Newhampshire and Vermont Journal vol. 5, no. 216 place: Walpole, NH, May 23, 1797; 055-005-A-1607; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 36)
      dimensions: 30cm x 50cm
    - The Freeman's Journal: or, the North-American Intelligencer no. 51 place: Philadelphia, Apr 10, 1782; 055-005-A-1612; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 37)
      dimensions: 27cm x 43cm
    - The Gazetteer and New Daily Advertiser no.15556 place: London, Dec 22, 1778; 055-005-A-1617; 4 pages (Box 15, Folder 38)
      dimensions: 30cm x 46cm
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 9, no. 451 place: Boston, Apr 10, 1777; 055-005-A-1622; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 11, no. 522 place: Boston, Aug 20, 1778; 055-005-A-1627; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 9, no. 467 place: Boston, Aug 7, 1777; 055-005-A-1632; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 517 place: Boston, Jul 16, 1778; 055-005-A-1637; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 515 place: Boston, Jul 2, 1778; 055-005-A-1642; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 518 place: Boston, Jul 23, 1778; 055-005-A-1647; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 516 place: Boston, Jul 9, 1778; 055-005-A-1652; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 9, no. 447 place: Boston, Mar 13, 1777; 055-005-A-1657; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 510 place: Boston, May 28, 1778; 055-005-A-1662; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 9, no.430 place: Boston, Nov 14, 1776; 055-005-A-1667; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no. 484 place: Boston, Nov 27, 1777; 055-005-A-1672; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 10, no.470 place: Boston, Oct 23, 1777; 055-005-A-1677; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol.9, no. 428 place: Boston, Oct 31, 1776; 055-005-A-1682; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 11, no. 574 place: Boston, Aug 19, 1779; 055-005-A-1687; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 642 place: Boston, Dec 14, 1780; 055-005-A-1692; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 641 place: Boston, Dec 8, 1780; 055-005-A-1697; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 11, no. 543 place: Boston, Jan 14, 1779; 055-005-A-1702; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
      dimensions: 25cm x 40cm
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 645 place: Boston, Jan 4, 1781; 055-005-A-1707; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 703 place: Boston, Jul 5, 1781; 055-005-A-1712; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vo. 13, no. 654 place: Boston, Mar 8, 1781; 055-005-A-1717; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 638 place: Boston, Nov 16, 1780; 055-005-A-1722; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 640 place: Boston, Nov 30, 1780; 055-005-A-1727; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 13, no. 635 place: Boston, Oct 26, 1780; 055-005-A-1732; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Chronicle and Universal Advertiser vol. 14, no. 683 place: Boston, Sep 17, 1781; 055-005-A-1737; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - The Independent Ledger and the American Advertiser vol. 5, no. 245 place: Boston, Jan 13, 1783; 055-005-A-1742; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 41)
      dimensions: 26cm x 30cm
    - The Independent Ledger and the American Advertiser vol. 5, no. 270 place: Boston, Jul 7, 1783; 055-005-A-1747; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - The Independent Ledger and the American Advertiser vol. 5, no. 256 place: Boston, Mar 31, 1783; 055-005-A-1752; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - The Independent Ledger and the American Advertiser vol. 3, no. 123 place: Boston, Oct 16, 1780; 055-005-A-1757; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - The Maryland Journal and Baltimore Advertiser vol. 4, no. 171 place: Baltimore, Feb 18, 1777; 055-005-A-1762; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - The Morning Post and Daily Advertiser no. 2390 place: London, Jun 22, 1780; 055-005-A-1767; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 43)
      dimensions: 33cm x 49cm
    - National Intelligencer. Washington Advertiser vol. 10, no. 1508 place: Washington City, PA, Jun 11, 1810; 055-005-A-1772; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 44)
      dimensions: 32cm x 50cm
    - New England Galaxy vol. 8, no. 410 place: Boston, Aug 19, 1825; 055-005-A-1777; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - New England Paladium vol. 30, no. 12 place: Boston, Aug 11, 1807; 055-005-A-1782; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 46)
      dimensions: 34cm x 56cm
    - New England Paladium vol. 35, no. 16 place: Boston, Feb 23, 1810; 055-005-A-1787; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 2, no. 87 place: Trenton, Aug 25, 1779; 055-005-A-1792; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
      dimensions: 24cm x 36cm
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 4, no. 165 place:Trenton, Feb 21, 1781; 055-005-A-1797; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 2, no. 83 place: Trenton, Jul 28, 1779; 055-005-A-1802; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 2, no. 82 place: Trenton, Jun 30, 1779; 055-005-A-1807; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 2, no. 67 place: Trenton, Mar 17, 1779; 055-005-A-1812; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 1, no. 45 place: Trenton, Oct 14, 1778; 055-005-A-1817; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 1, no. 45 place: Trenton, Oct 14, 1778; 055-005-A-1817; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 3, no. 147 place: Trenton, Oct 18, 1780; 055-005-A-1827; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The New-Jersey Gazette vol. 2, no. 91 place: Trenton, Sep 22, 1779; 055-005-A-1832; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - The Pennsylvania Gazette no. 2498 place: Philadelphia, Nov 6, 1776; 055-005-A-1837; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Pennsylvania Journal no. 1419 (Supplement) place: Philadelphia, Feb 15, 1770; 055-005-A-1842; 2 pages (Box 16, Folder 49)
      physical description: half sheet; newspaper
      dimensions: 26cm x 41cm
    - The Pennsylvania Ledger: or, the Virginia, Maryland, Pennsylvania and New-Jersey Weekly Advertiser no. 95 place: Philadelphia, Nov 16, 1776; 055-005-A-1845; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - The Providence Gazette and Country Journal no. 386 place: Providence, Jun 1, 1771; 055-005-A-1850; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 51)
      physical description: full sheet in folio, top left corner missing; newspaper
    - The Providence Gazette and Country Journal vol. 13, no. 669 place: Providence, Oct 26, 1776; 055-005-A-1855; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - The St. James's Chronicle; or, British Evening-post no. 2517 place: London, Apr 29, 1777; 055-005-A-1860; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 52)
      dimensions: 31cm x 46cm
    - The St. James's Chronicle; or, British Evening-post no. 2490 place: London, Feb 25, 1777; 055-005-A-1865; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - The St. James's Chronicle; or, British Evening-post no. 2534 place: London, Jun 7, 1777; 055-005-A-1870; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - The Salem Gazette vol. 35, no.66 place: Salem, Aug 17, 1821; 055-005-A-1875; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 53)
      dimensions: 35cm x 53cm
    - Salem Register vol. 49, no. 14 place: Salem, Feb 17, 1848; 055-005-A-1880; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 54)
      physical description: wove paper; newspaper
      dimensions: 48cm x 63cm
    - Salem Register vol. 49, no. 20 place: Salem, Mar 9, 1848; 055-005-A-1885; 4 pages (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - A List of the Officers Prisoner in New York place: s.l., Sep 5, 1776; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 55)
      physical description: half sheet, a.d.
      extent: 1 page
      dimensions: 20cm x 24.5cm
    - A List of the Killed and Wounded, of His Majesty's forces at the engagement of Bunker's-Hill A List of the Killed, Wounded, and Missing of His Majesty's forces under the Command of His Excellency the Honourable General Howe in the several Engagements and Skirmishes with the Provincials from the Taking of Long Island, August 27th, to the Close of that Campaign, 8th December, 1776 place: s.l., Jun 17, 1775-Dec 8, 1776; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 56)
      dimensions: 18.5cm x 25cm
    - The New York Packet and the American Advertiser No. 200 (Facsimile) place: Fishkill, Feb 1, 1781; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 57)
      physical description: laminated facsimile, newspaper
      dimensions: 23cm x 41cm
    - creator: Isaac Requa, Benjamin Morgan, Samuel Lyon, Joshua Purdy, Elijah Ward, Clark Mead place: White Plains, Apr 15, 1801; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 58)
      physical description: full sheet, a.l.s.
      dimensions: 32cm x 19cm
    - Proposals, for Printing by Subscription, The Political and Military Works, Miscellaneous Collections, from the Papers of the late Major-General Charles Lee place: Baltimore, Jun 10, 1785; 1 pages (Box 16, Folder 59)
      Includes signature of one subscriber, Sam H. Parson of Middletown.
      physical description: folio leaf, a.d.s.
      dimensions: 46cm x 37cm
    - Private Room of Sir Henry Clinton No. 1 Broadway place: New York, 1858; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 60)
      physical description: half sheet, lithograph print
      dimensions: 18cm x 11cm
    - Arrestation du Major Andre au Bourg Tarry Town place: s.l., Undated; 1 pages (Box 14, Folder 61)
      General Physical Desription
      physical description: half sheet, steel engraving print
      dimensions: 21.5cm x 13.5cm